what do you think of me when you think
of me the first time we met what do you
remember I think of you the first time
we met yeah when you think of the first
time we met what do you remember I
remember you stood up to greet me and I
was pleasantly surprised by that um cute
hair cute face great smile
I was really excited you know because
I'd seen you online but first time in
person and it was it was great that you
were just as every bit as attractive as
I thought you a relief and yeah you you
fixed my hair I asked you to fix my hair
and you fixed my hair yeah I like that
that wasn't even a second thought I said
can you fix my hair yeah I said yeah and
you leaned over you fixed my hair and
you're very smiley and very sweet okay
mentioned before me standing up always
like standing out to you yeah well why
do you think that is I don't know it was
just a really sweet thing like you
seemed eager and excited and present and
that standing up kind of represents all
of that not in like a you know m'lady
not in a m'lady sort of way just just
you know you I don't need you to hold
doors open or anything but I just like
that you're you know you don't that you
you stood up and that it seemed like you
were excited for me to join you at the
table and I like that yeah what about me
I remember your smile I mean just
you know because you're I'm sitting
there I'm waiting I'm trying to kind of
maybe look busy not always looking at
the door waiting for the person that
looks like the photo to walk in the
person I've been talking to and then
when you came in and so obviously so
clearly you and that was very exciting
because you matched up with the image I
had built up as well just just very
quickly and how you expressed yourself
you know just in the moment to the
presence of course I remember yes that
big smile yeah taking up 90% of your
face and I don't I didn't think it was a
conscious choice to stand up here just
like that's yeah of course like oh I'm
gonna walk closer and say hi I remember
you being really animated very energetic
maybe it's because of what that guy was
it like a cow the cacao candy thing
basically cocaine basically cocaine but
I didn't mean to yes yeah it was great
yeah so you know this was like a first
day thing so in a way and sometimes you
know as the talkative kind of person you
know I end up finding myself having to
lead conversations and having toys drive
that momentum and all any any sense of
you know like weights or you know it was
upcoming difficulty was just dissipated
like within 30 seconds yeah it felt like
we knew each other yeah that's nice
comfortable exactly yeah all right is
the next question
when do you feel closest to me in some
ways may be lazy mornings you know just
in that physical intimacy of that just
being able to lay together be very
comfortable be good yeah
nuzzle it up I know so after after good
sex after that that sense of you know
that we managed to really satisfy each
other and that we were connected and
that that emotional connection was there
as well and we can just kind of bask in
in our in our abilities and in our in
our at each other it's I feel very loved
and it's it's it's a very nice feeling
yeah well yeah I guess those moments we
are together in our own space yeah how
are you know I agree with you about sex
post-sex you know I just but I think
also when we're creating something
together when we're writing together and
it just feels really productive and I
say something and then you say something
and then I write something and then you
do something and and it just feels like
we're building off this momentum and I
just feel like it's such an obvious
closeness that we have that we can we
can bounce those things around really
quickly and and have something to show
for that just like I don't know shows
how close we are it's not a competition
well what are you hesitant
tell me has a tenth of Terra yeah yeah
Wow I I don't I don't know I feel like
we share everything you know I mean you
know about issues in my past and exes
and crushes and you know any a lot of
the things that couples are hesitant to
share or never do or you know my kinks
or my you know my annoyances and
grievances like those those are things
that we talk about constantly so I
really don't feel like I ever hesitate
to share anything with you probably
sometimes you wish I would maybe
hesitate a bit more sharing things but I
really you know I you know that I can't
as soon as something comes up I have to
tell you even if it's not at the right
time so there's no question you were
like oh I hope that's not a question
that eh yeah no you know and I've been
thinking about it the last couple days
and there hasn't been anything that I'm
like oh god I really I feel like I am as
open as I can be with someone with you
yeah is there anything you're hesitant I
think anything that was a reluctance at
any point I've already shared with you
you know there were any parts that maybe
I was insecure about or oh you know I've
been really shared this part of myself
completely yet I definitely feel like I
have there are no it's sighs it's not
exciting right that's not I wish there
is like a little something I never told
you about it
yeah first unfortunate lack of the
excitement of it no yeah
[Laughter]
what was the last trip that connected us
and why the last trip that connected us
yeah and why I know we go on somewhat
each other we do or one of the the best
trip that I linked at us anyway what
comes to mind is Israel you know what
you asked that question something last
trip I by any means but yeah because you
know yeah I saw you visit you in
Istanbul then there's that time apart
and then relatively quickly it felt we
you know travel together to Israel to to
go to Jordan and all that and that was
you know intense weekend a bit of us
just traveling and figuring out each
other's rhythms no Wade you know known
each other for what like three months
pretty much yeah and most of its through
a computer screen yeah so you know you
think you saw me as me and I gonna see
you as you and I think it was exciting
to get our ideas of each other confirmed
to you know be pushed into a highly kind
of stressful situation but of course oh
so this was our earlier can I trip
together so maybe there was some aspect
or we got our best behavior or this that
but I'd like to think otherwise and you
know I I was there a bit longer and then
we talked while I was outside the museum
and we talked about what you're gonna be
doing next summer and whether you'd be
coming to the Netherlands or waiting so
it was highly kind of emotional and
exciting to
find out what that conclusion was going
to be and that you did decide to come
sooner than later I was maybe a bit
worried that you would feel like you
would we're going to miss out on one
thing that you really wanted instead of
the other thing but I think I like to
think the way the right choice said I'm
not really happy that you came he did so
yeah that really connected us I feel I I
was thinking the trip the latest trip
that connected us was best kept secret
the festival you know we had a little
road trip down there to the south and
then we worked on building this festival
together I just saw you had like some
manual labor and you know waking up
early and trekking to the site and then
your second all-time it was so sick but
we you know we push through and we met
people and and we were camping and not
really sleeping because it's a festival
I don't know what we were expecting but
you know actually literally sharing a
tiny tent and not the best weather and
but then we had those that moment when
the festival doors opened and we were
all like standing there together and
seeing what we had created or been part
of creating and then we got to actually
stay for the whole festival and
experience that music and Sunday morning
I think was it like really solidified
that connection for us for me you know
happy like lying there in the morning
and listening to agree with Jonny
Greenwood and the orchestra and it was
like raining and relying on the picnic
blanket and you know we're a little
hungover from the weekend but you're
holding hands and just like really in
that music really connected yeah and
then stumbling upon some other bands
before leaving tora tora and then
sitting on the beach across from the
festival before leaving just listening
to an echoing across the
as I was really great yeah I felt really
really connected to you yeah
what is the biggest challenge to our
relationship and how do you think we can
solve it biggest challenge I don't think
it's lack of communication but I think
it's sometimes finding the right way to
communicate what we need to communicate
I think that that just comes from being
different people alright coming from
different families and different
countries and and having and as similar
as we are in so many ways and even as
our families are you know the way that
you express yourself sometimes is it's
hard for me to interpret you know and
and but we're learning we're learning
how to figure that out as we go along
and I think we're both patient people
and will over communicate until we
figure out why we can't communicate and
then continue to communicate so I think
that that works for us you know wanting
to communicate and wanting to figure out
exactly why why is there confusion here
why aren't we understanding one another
and figuring out so we're we're we're
working on it I mean I've been I've been
and really just before we're talking too
much was actually the problem I mean in
some ways because they've just become
this cycle of trying to talk about the
issue and talking about that issue which
cause another issue which got another I
should not obviously those weren't
didn't create a healthy relationship I
mean is that a worry you would ever have
that would over communicate things no
I'm I'm not worried about that because I
think that we both like like to have a
conclusion you know we like it to to get
somewhere and so I don't think we leave
things open ended you know you know you
don't like to go to bed without solving
whatever issues at hand
and I think that's a good way to be and
I think we kind of do that regardless of
it's nighttime or daytime you know
wherever we are we want to make sure we
resolve whatever the thing it is we need
to talk about and usually we do so
pretty quickly because yeah we listen to
each other and we figure it out oh you
want me to yeah why not the biggest
challenge in our relationship um I think
that yeah well you talk about one aspect
I think for some ways we're going to
we're gonna have to figure out how we
balance our you know ambitions as they
relate to you know creativity to our
careers to you know how we want to
survive as as people and how that
connects into our relationship and you
know that that level of partnership as
well you know you talked about the
intimacy you feel when we work together
and I feel - so that's a very exciting
thing but I I suspect maybe I'm just
seeing about being anxious but I suspect
that the owners gonna be challenges
facing that as well and you know as we
try and find our place more yeah we're
still kind of both searching a bit so I
think part of that challenge which
doesn't seem insurmountable seems like
something we can definitely handle is
how how are we gonna move forward
together how are we gonna collectively
find go towards our ambitions and that's
it's it's an exciting challenge in a way
that's it's fun to think that that is
probably the biggest thing we're gonna
have to deal with yeah yeah it's a biter
yeah
when was the last time I disappointed
you and how do you feel about it now
that's actually at the at the Film
Festival at the blik - nothing
yes yeah I mean that's the last thing I
can think about the last time you know I
was minor relative and minor we had to
do this kind of thing just you know and
together with all the other people
sitting in the theater sitting outside
the theater and I think they asked a
question if yeah if you were - how would
you seduce me and in my mind was like
okay so yeah how would I say this er
just like as we are and then you said
something and then I misinterpreted it
as say like we don't know each other and
then I'd you know you know yeah I
attempted to do then that thing and then
I felt like I put myself like okay I'm
gonna pretend she's someone I don't know
ish and I'm gonna do whatever ability to
flirt that I have and then I felt at the
time you guys shut it down because it
wasn't what the actual assignment was so
what disappointed me was that I I felt
yeah I felt like you know I'm like
almost as if I'm at like asking a girl
out to be like Roy and it bummed me out
but and then we got like into like a
little argument right there in the
moment which felt like it too obvious
which frustrated me as well like oh
great they got to us already yeah that's
before we signed up for this thing and
but we talked about it right then and
there and you know he said you're sorry
and then I explained what I was going on
my hands and then we and we worked it
out so that's it
after all that gold you ever see her
yeah
one two test test
seduction sex yeah so we talked about it
we talked it through it was you know
obviously a minor thing but uh I guess I
just felt vulnerable so you felt
disappointed though me yeah I was
disappointed that I was disappointed
that I couldn't just you know play that
game and disappointed that you work in a
responds and I guess I'll wait it out
smashing noise I guess that's
disappointed also yeah like disappointed
in I didn't it didn't work I didn't -
this year and my so far with you in the
way that I hoped I would okay yeah yeah
how about you disappointed me that time
you didn't bring the picnic blanket you
know now uh disappointed me I'm s that's
pretty strong you know for me hmm if
someone disappoints me you know it's
like it's like when I'm not that I'm
comparing this to being a mother but you
know what I mean like when a mom is
disappointed that's like the worst thing
right it's a nursing degree
yeah we're not disappointed right yeah
so to me that's that's like stronger
it's more serious than like being
frustrated or being angry being
disappointed is like yeah letting
someone down and you know that that's
like the that's the hardest thing for me
it's like let myself roll let people
down so
you you disappointed me yeah now that
you've explained how serious honestly I
can't think of okay when you came to
Istanbul to visit and I felt like you
know you I had to work the day that you
arrived and you're flying all the way
from Amsterdam and it was the first time
we'd be seeing each other after meeting
here and then me going back home to
Istanbul and you weren't sure what you
were going to do the whole first day
because there'd be no way for me to let
you into my apartment you wouldn't know
where it was and I had to work until
like 6:00 or 7:00 p.m. so I created this
whole plan for you so you would have
like interesting things to see in places
to go and you wouldn't feel so lost in
such a city of chaos and I made this old
book and I talked to all these different
cafes and I I planned like different
routes for you and like different games
for you to play and I drew photos and I
drew a map and and then you showed up
and you're like oh my friends picking me
up so I'll see you later and I'm gonna
stay with him for the first couple days
and that like really really disappointed
me because I felt like I was so excited
to see you and I put so much effort into
yeah you know like a high school project
you know but I like I really put on my
heart into this and then you're just
like yeah yeah my friends picking me up
I'm gonna go stay in this like fancy
area of the city I'll see you in a
couple days yeah okay I don't think I
stayed there a couple days really
that's two days the first two days
[Laughter]
what is something I could have done to
support you during the abortion I think
I think he did a pretty good job
supporting me I think it would have been
you know I was I was mostly nervous
about interacting with the doctors that
would that was my biggest concern you
know of course I honestly it wasn't as
emotional about making that big choice
as I think it is for a lot of people it
wasn't as hard for me I knew the choice
that I wanted to make and that probably
was best for us as well obviously it was
best for us but yeah I knew that I
wanted to have an abortion so that
wasn't a big decision but for going to
the intake appointment by myself and
then having to make the decision do I
take the pill or you know do I come back
and have a surgery and am I fully under
or do I just do it with like local
anesthesia you know like what and -
making these choices that was really
hard for me and having that doctor who
wasn't very nice and you know that that
makes me like really emotional
more so vivid than anything else feeling
vulnerable already and then being by
myself and not having that support I
know you had to work but it was it was
hard and then what you weren't there or
something oh your friends were in town
that was the week before yeah your
friends were in town but I still like I
went and got tested to make sure that I
was they did the ultrasound to make sure
I was actually pregnant okay they're in
the same time this day your friends
arrived and you you wanted me to no no
no I do the pregnancy I took the
pregnancy test yeah
and then they were arriving like an
authority but the moment that your best
friends were arriving into town and you
kind of had encouraged me to take it and
then you went and hung out with them and
I was by myself at home like taking this
pregnancy test and I just felt like you
know maybe didn't realize like how how
emotional that would be yeah I remember
that conversation I mean I understand I
understand why you felt that I was
encouraging it at the time I thought
about this obviously recently and what
would have had been if you had waited a
few days and then taking it like you
know schrödinger's pregnancy or
something like what would have it
changed the dynamic wise I just remember
being on the phone with you and you
saying that you got the you got the test
or something and what I recall I said
like you know if you want to decide to
take it now that's sure if not that's
okay too
your probably sensed because you know me
that I like knowing things right away so
you felt that encouragement I think you
said I would rather you take the
pregnancy test now
why would why would we need to wait and
for me it was a matter of whether I'm
pregnant or not it is what it is at
least we can wait a couple days until
your friends leave your best friends
that you haven't seen in years yeah and
and you were kind of like let's just
let's just figure it out now let's just
know and that is one big difference
between you rather just like no now no
matter what and me it's like well it is
what it is let's just like wait wait to
open the box sure neighbor's cat or
whatever but okay but I think yeah just
just being a little more present and
then you did end up staying the next day
with me after the day I had the abortion
you stayed with me but then the next day
you were kind of just you were gonna go
do something else with some friends
you're gonna meet up with friends and
you go you're okay and I told you like
I'm not okay like I know that I seem
okay but I need your hair and you didn't
you stayed
so that you didn't provide the support
that I needed yeah because it was hard
to read sometimes exactly what you're
you know because yeah like you said it
wasn't it didn't have the stereotypical
kind of emotional white that you know
like whoa well one sided are we playing
every like making not to make it too
much of a big deal are we gonna push the
side it's like oh you know this is what
it is we'll move on or like oh my god
let's individual yeah so trying to find
that balance yeah that I think you know
you you were you got me any medicine I
needed you brought me food you got a hot
water bottle
you don't like everything and you're you
yeah everything you could do to help you
you were trying to do so you're very
very supportive and and present one shot
once I let you know that I needed you to
be good
do you really think we'll last yeah why
[Laughter]
that was enthusiastic yeah yeah this is
Suzy astok yes it's confident about it I
I see I see us I feel I feel we were
just we're in a committed relationship
yeah it's it's we're there we've
committed we we talked about the future
we imagined it we fantasize about the
possibilities and I you know probably
for longer than it was concrete for us
both knowing for sure I was always just
considering how things would be down the
line and whatever I imagined myself in
the future I always imagined it together
with you and I
I just I trust the dynamic we have I
feel I feel lucky to to be able to share
it share my experiences with you and to
be a part of my life it's such a
comforting and nice feeling and that's
if I am a bit if I'm happy that I can
infect you with my happiness or if I am
down that you will lift me up you're the
first person you know if I'm if I have
something interesting to say I want to
tell it to you first and you have so
many interesting things to tell me
inside as enjoy our conversations so
dearly it's just such a joy and that
really gives me a lot of confidence that
you were we're gonna last for sure and
if anything were to happen for whatever
reason if things were to change for us I
I know that we will just we'll figure it
out we will do what is best for one
another and where I just we care for
each other a lot so well do what we can
to make sure that we cause this little
pain as possible and it's nice to be
able to just know that see that in you
you're a nice your kind person or good
person
that's important do you want me to
answer yeah tape it up nothing I've ever
said ditto
yeah yeah I guess yeah forever love ya
we have forever love you know and I I
came to this discovery pretty early on
that what I have for you and what we
have for each other is forever love so
whatever that means you know even if we
didn't get married and we end up not
having children or you know whatever is
in store plenty of cats I mean I'm not
worried about that but whatever is in
store for us and we still have that
forever love that connection so will
last in whatever way that means yeah
forever love
what do you think I'm missing out by
being with you well I mean you're you're
younger than me you're 25 yes yes I am
age doesn't matter it's just a number
right 17 you're 25 and I'm 29 and I I
feel like I've lived 10 lives you know I
feel so lucky to have been able to live
in so many places and do so many things
and and have adventures and meet amazing
people and things I know you've done as
well but I feel like I've had more
opportunities to do so just because I'm
older and you know sometimes I find
myself saying when I was your age and I
don't mean it in that like I'm older
sort of way but like I'm like oh yeah
when I was 25 I was living in Istanbul I
was doing this I was Anna and I feel
like sometimes being with me and
settling down is somehow might limit you
and in whatever way that means and
however that turns out and I I don't
ever want to limit you like I love you
and all I want is for you to be happy
and to grow and to learn and and to be
able to witness those changes and and
growth and I I don't know what I would
do if I found out I was limiting you in
some way that I would just break my
heart so I I hope that I never do and I
hope that that the way that we are
together just continues to encourage
growth and change and
that can be limitless you know I'm not
I'm so not worried about your limiting
me in any way I mean what what what's
exciting for me and what I love also
about being with you is that I if
anything you're just going to encourage
more experiences for me yeah that idea
of settling down or that I'll be limited
because I'm with maybe it was a
different partner if it was someone else
who is more set and doesn't have an
interest in growth or expanding that
would be a different question you know
that age difference because it's with
you there's someone I think who is going
to pull the best out of me so if I I
know I'm not gonna miss out on anything
being with you it's gonna just help me
get more okay I'm glad you feel that way
yeah
looking back do you wish you'd proposed
why or why not
[Laughter]
I was because because you know as you
know you know our first discussion is
this idea we had these conversations
about the idea of marriage before and
you had expressed in so many terms that
not for you yeah marriage whatever some
bullshit patriarchy system that's good
but there's no need for it so I kind of
I think I resigned to the idea like okay
that's that's what that is
you know that's not something that's
necessary for me to have a relationship
with her so when you did propose to me
it's and make it had to make me it's
like it's gonna look that back-and-forth
almost like if I was I was up it was a
you know so in the moment as well so on
the moment of like a heightened
experience of like us being outs and you
know traveling and being with friends
and having a great time and then like
you said I want to marry you
that it almost was difficult to like
process it at once like is this for real
is this you know a sincere and truthful
moment right here and there you didn't
believe it
no I of course but you know you always
sincere about these things it's not like
you ever take those things back it's
just it was a low is hard to reconcile
with what I had thoughts your ideology
was before which is why I said yes but
let's I want to ask you again the next
day to make sure
I don't regret not being the one to
propose I like the fact that there's
this yeah and the role reversal of its I
enjoy that I don't know I'll be honest I
don't know if I would have asked myself
as soon as you asked me I think if I
were the one who's like oh you know the
guy I'm going to ask at some point it
probably would have been at a different
points and I've probably been more I
want to have been more of a thing to
some degree not like it would have been
more of a thing I just did a little bit
no no no need a no flash my house or
whatever nonsense no fancy restaurant
dinners okay it's like inside the
chocolate tarts are but I imagine I
would have been like ha you know how am
I gonna ask it and do I deal with a ring
I partner I think it would I would I
maybe I miss the fun of like dealing
with that I yeah that's kind of like all
my thoughts scattered around I hope that
answers it to some degree yeah okay what
about you do they feel happy that you
were the ones asked absolutely yeah I
honestly if you had asked I I don't I
don't know I because I would have felt
like you weren't you didn't trust my
feelings about marriage you know mm-hmm
you're like oh oh she'll just she'll
ventually come around so if I ask her
then she'll feel differently about
marriage well it would have been true
yes but I had to come to that
realization on my own I would have felt
like it was forced upon me by you
putting me on the spot like that
mm-hm I think I don't know who knows but
I I'm I'm really glad the way that the
way that it happened what's fair
okay and now I did not ask them I didn't
ask for this one
what do you admire most about me are you
sure yeah that's a hard one the most
what do I admire most about you there
are so many things don't worry we don't
have that time ya know but doing my most
aside from your sense of fashion I think
I admire your your drive and your
determination to follow your vision to
follow what you think is right and what
needs to be done and and sometimes
that's in a human interaction and
sometimes that's in work and sometimes
that's in your creativity but whatever
it is you know what you want and you go
for it and you give it your all you know
but you do you when you're passionate
about something there's there's no
denying it you put your whole self into
it and I I love that about you I really
it's inspiring
i-i-i was and i remain just rain pressed
by the person you decided you wanted to
be and how you made those choices to get
there that you knew what environment you
want to be so you move there yeah that
you you you you know left left your
space at a young age I'm gonna go
somewhere else and this is where I'm
gonna start my life and yeah from what I
know also from what you've told me that
you commit to those decisions that you
you you've seen the people around you
who make easier choices that you don't
make easy choices for yourself it's it's
very impressive I know you sometimes
feel you know so has the older one that
you're still not a hundred percent you
haven't figured out life completely yet
it's somehow your responsibility that
you have to but I like that's you're
searching and that you're so eager for
discovery and adventure and that you
know more than me are always willing to
try new things and to that your game or
pretty much any kind of interesting
experience
that is I think that's a driven need to
be a very kind person you really it's
important to you that the experiences
you've had help you grow and it just
makes me makes me proud to be with you
you are yeah you're impressive and your
sense of experimentation and adventure
I really wanted that about you last one
yeah okay
why do you love me
hmm I guess I'm kind of covered it yeah
absolutely
yeah you can tell me more everything
I've said of this session the fact that
we're here that this is something we
both wanted to do that you know that yes
maybe it feeds since you are its are
like egos have been or a nurse's ism you
know the attention but also just the
idea that you are secure enough and
confident of that what we have that our
relationship can also just be broadcast
out there
we know that well that the love we have
is can be put up to scrutiny this degree
I love I love you and I love everything
I said before but you know that your
kindness your sexiness
that's what venture your spirit your
generosity and your constant efforts to
help us grow and I really love that you
find intimacy in the fact that you know
things that I just just you know with
the discovery our conversation intimacy
and how we work together that that our
creativity our ambitions
are part of us hey you laugh a lot
it helps I do yeah yeah oh you want me
dancing I feel I feel very loved right
now yeah I mean I feel like I've just
been answering it exact time but I don't
have to lay it out okay
I mean I usually do you know hmm before
we go to bed okay I'm gonna be down the
line how do I love thee let me name the
ways I yeah I love all the things that I
mentioned earlier and and I also really
love how you love not just how you love
me you know that's that's fantastic
but how you love your parents and how
you love your friends and how you love